let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: ' "I have never been to Russia. I think I shall go there next year.” said Bill. ',
    answer: "Bill said that he had never been to Russia and he thought he would go there the next year.",
    options: [
      "Bill said that he had never been to Russia and he thought he would go there the next year.",
      "Bill said that he would have never been to Russia and he thinks he would go there the next year.",
      "Bill said that he had never been to Russia and he thinks he will go there the next year.",
      "Bill said that he has never been to Russia and he thinks he would go there the next year."
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: ' "People believed that Jane retired because of her poor health. ',
    answer: "Jane was believed to have retired because of her poor health.",
    options: [
      "Jane is believed to have retired because of her poor health.",
      "Jane was believed to have retired because of her poor health.",
      "It is believed that Jane retired because of her poor health.",
      "Jane retired because of her poor health was believed."
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: " The government knows the extent of the problem. The government needs to take action soon. ",
    answer: "Knowing the extent of the problem, the government needs to take action soon.",
    options: [
      "The government knows the extent of the problem whereas it needs to take action soon.",
      "The government knows the extent of the problem so that it needs to take action soon.",
      "Knowing the extent of the problem, the government needs to take action soon.",
      "The government knows the extent of the problem, or else it needs to take action soon."
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: " The substance is very toxic. Protective clothing must be worn at all times. ",
    answer: "So toxic is the substance that protective clothing must be worn at all times.",
    options: [
      "Since the substance is very toxic, so protective clothing must be worn at all times.",
      "So toxic is the substance that protective clothing must be worn at all times.",
      "The substance is such toxic that protective clothing must be worn at all times.",
      "The substance is too toxic to wear protective clothing at all times."
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: " John is studying hard. He doesn’t want to fail the exam. ",
    answer: "John is studying hard in Oder not to fail the next exam",
    options: [
      "John is studying hard in Oder not to fail the next exam",
      "John is studying hard in Oder that he not fail the next exam",
      "John is studying hard so as to fail the next exam",
      "John is studying hard in Oder to not to fail the next exam"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: " She gave in her notice. She planned to start her new job in January ",
    answer: "She gave in her notice with a view to starting her new job in January",
    options: [
      "She gave in her notice, plan to start her new job in January",
      "She gave in her notice with a view to starting her new job in January",
      "Her notice was given in with an aim to start her new job in January",
      "Her notice was given in order for her to start her new job in January."
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: " When the unemployment rate is high, the crime rate is usually also high. ",
    answer: "The higher the unemployment rate is, the higher the crime rate is.",
    options: [
      "The unemployment rate and the crime rate are both higher.",
      "The higher the unemployment rate is, the higher the crime rate is.",
      "The unemployment rate is as high as the crime rate.",
      "The high rate of unemployment depends on the high rate of crime."
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: " I wish you had not said that",
    answer: "It would be nice if you had not said that.",
    options: [
      "I wish you not to say that.",
      "If only you did not say that",
      "I hope you will not say that.",
      "It would be nice if you had not said that."
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: " “You are always making terrible mistakes”, said the teacher. ",
    answer: "The teacher complained about his students making terrible mistakes.",
    options: [
      "The teacher asked his students why they always made terrible mistakes.",
      "The teacher realized that his students always made terrible mistakes.",
      "The teacher complained about his students making terrible mistakes.",
      "The teacher made his students not always make terrible mistakes."
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: " There is no point in your phoning Jane – she’s away. ",
    answer: "It would be a waste of time phoning Jane – she’s away.",
    options: [
      "It would be a waste of time phoning Jane – she’s away.",
      "You waste your time if you insist on phoning Jane – she’s away.",
      "Don’t spend your valuable time phoning Jane – she’s out.",
      "Jane is very difficult to phone – she’s always away."
    ]
  },
];